# 嗨喽大家好我是王刚
Hello everyone, I am Wang Gang.
# 之前 也不是之前
In the past days…maybe earlier,
# 反正一两年来总有粉丝要问
Anyway, every once in a while some fans will ask me,
# 我们这个专业设备买来适不适合家里面用
Should they buy a professional cooking system for home use.
# 今天我就买一套来告诉大家
Today I will demonstrate
# 不适合家里用
How it doesn’t work for home use.
# 然后跟大家介绍一下这个工程款的炉灶
I will also introduce to you the professional cooking stove.
# 师傅 我们这个灶还是你来介绍吧
Sir, please do the introduction,
# 你要专业一点
You are the professional.
# 这个灶属于是油气两用
This multi fuel stove works with both diesel and gas.
# 它其实还可以三用 它液化气也能用
Actually it works with LPG, too.
# 嗯 对
Yes, that’s right.
# 然后这里这个是天然气的开关
Now, here it is the switch for natural gas.
# 这个是烧油的那个开关
And this is the switch for diesel.
# 油开关嘛反正
OK the oil switch.
# 然后下面这个是风机的开关
Underneath here it is the switch for the fan.
# 它这个灶的风机功率特别大
This stove's fan power is higher than most of the others.
# 所以它这个只要一台风机就够了
Therefore it only needs one fan.
# 然后像这个高端的好一点的那个灶都配了这种
And higher end stoves like this all have
# 就是那边有一个水可以直接洗灶台的这种
the (advanced) running water system to conveniently clean the cooking area
# 方便一点
Make things easier
# OK 我来补充一下
OK, let me add some more details about this
# 我们这一款的话是工程灶 超大型的
What we have here is an oversized engineering level stove
# 长2米 宽是116厘米
It is 2 meters long, 116 centimeters wide
# 是116吧
Is it 116 centimeters?
# 对对对
Yes, that is correct.
# 116厘米
116 centimeters.
# 然后我们这个宽度的话是非常宽
And the width is extra wide too.
# 然后高的话大概是80（厘米）的样子
The height is about 80 centimeters.
# 79-80（厘米）
79-80 centimeters.
# 我们这个灶是酒店里面的专业款
This stove is the professional version for restaurants.
# 然后很多粉丝他说看我们在厨房里面炒菜
Many fans said they really love the way we cook in the kitchen
# 他觉得这一款如果在自己家里面买一套的话就非常好
And they want the same cooking system in their own homes, which feels good.
# 其实我想告诉你
But I would really want to tell you,
# 你们家里面的厨房拿都拿不进去 首先第一点
It would not fit a home kitchen. First of all,
# 宽都这么宽
It is very wide.
# 然后是什么呢
Second…
# 我们这个灶是费了很大力气
We made an ultimate effort
# 六七个人抬下来
With 6-7 people carried it together,
# 这个灶有八百斤没有
Does this stove weight around 400 KG (880 lbs)?
# 差不多
Very close estimate.
# 差不多八百斤
Around 400 KG.
# 以前的灶它还更加重
The former one was even heavier.
# 因为它里面是弄的水泥是吧
Is it because it was built with cement inside?
# 对对对
Yes, that is right.
# 现在它不是水泥 现在要减轻一点
This one has no cement, therefore it weighs less.
# 然后这一套设备除了酒店里面用的话没有其他什么地方用
Would any other facilities use this kind of equipment beside restaurants?
# 其他地方用的话就是用再小一点的
Other facilities would use smaller versions.
# 小的尺寸是多少
What are the dimensions of the smaller versions?
# 小的是有1米55乘以80（厘米）的
Some are like 1.55 meters by 80 centimeters.
# 还有那个1米75乘80
Also there is 1.75 meters by 80 centimeters.
# 哦 宽是80
OK, so the width would be 80 meters.
# 对对对
That is right.
# 高度都是差不多一样高的
The height is always almost the same.
# 所有厨房的东西都差不多高
All the kitchen stuff are the same height.
# 比方说包括操作台那些东西都是一样高 都是80
For instance things including countertops are always 80 centimeters high.
# 所以说家里面用这个不是买一个灶就可以了
So for home use, buying a stove is only the beginning
# 还要有上面的抽风机
Also you will need a range hood.
# 要不然这个油烟非常的大
Otherwise the cooking smoke will be overwhelming.
# 然后还有一个原因是什么呢
And another reason that makes it impractical is
# 它下面有一个鼓风机
There should be a blower under there.
# 这个鼓风机550瓦 非常的吵
This blower’s power is 550 Walt, very noisy
# 因为农村的柴火都比较小
In the countryside, we use firewood, and the power is low
# 炒菜达不到我想要的那种效果
I cannot get the result I want.
# 用惯了这个灶 用柴火灶有点不习惯
I am now used to this stove, and not so used to firewood stoves.
# 所以现在买一套来练一下手
So I want to purchase this for the purpose of practice.
# 好 师傅你继续吧
OK sir, you may continue.
# 弄好了我好来试一下
I will try it when you finish.
# 好了 我们这个灶已经电接好了 气也接好了
OK, now the electric part of the stove is all finished, as well as the gas connection.
# 现在就先试一下
Let’s try it.
# 火能不能吹起来
To see if the flame can be blown to a good level.
# 电帮我开一下
Please help me to turn the power on.
# 好 可以 差不多
OK, not bad, looks good.
# 再试下另外一个
Let’s try the other stove top.
# 没有问题 没有什么大问题
No problem, no big issue.
# 现在就差水了是吧
Now we just need the water, right?
# 现在水接上就可以了
Yeah, just the water.
# 好了 这个放一点水进去
OK, let’s pour some water in.
# 因为我们这个干烧的话
If we heated it dry,
# 这个气从这里出去 热量从这里出去
Air will go out here as well as the heat.
# 所以这个里面要放点水
So we will need some water in here.
# 这边把水给它放上的话
When we have some water here
# 它使用的寿命就会更加的长
The service life will be longer.
# 所以我们在视频里面会看到它这个水管会一直水流个不停
So in our videos you have seen this faucet always running
# 就是为了降温度 降温用的
It is for cooling down
# 如果不给它降温的话 这里温度会非常高
If not cooling things down, the temperature will be too high
# 这些地方 还有这里都会烧坏
Here and here….these places will be burnt out.
# 好了 本期视频就到这里了
OK, that is all for today’s video.
# 待会儿把这个撕掉 这个灶就非常的漂亮了
I will tear this off in a second, then the stove will look even nicer!